Tell me what you want extra and let's
set it up.
>> I would like to know what's inside of
this without having to cut it open.
>> You see how everything else on here is
one color? It looks like it's, you know,
iron deposits.
>> Blocking X-ray.
>> I know. Mletus did not make an X-ray
proof artifact.
>> Okay, he got through that one.
>> Okay, now you're seeing something there.
>> Now, what is that?
>> I want to see if there's a duracell in
one of these. Power source must be in
here. In this one, the power source is
not in this. It's in this.
>> Do you think they got a battery in there
somehow?
>> I don't see how.
>> Tell them how you how we met.
>> I think you were struggling when I
[laughter] was up a mountain in Alabama.
As I recall, coming up that mountain,
you were cramping. I said, "I've got
these electrolyte pills here. If you
don't mind taking a pill from a
stranger, and you just took it right
away. [laughter] You didn't think
>> they had caffeine in them. It was bad.
>> I couldn't sleep at all that night.
>> I [laughter] didn't sleep awake either.
I came back and I ran the 50 mileer and
I won that guy.
>> Oh yeah, you did.
>> Let's [laughter]
tell me what you want to X-ray and let's
set it up. I'm curious. You want to
X-ray what's in here or do you want the
crystals?
>> I'd like to see what's
>> Let's put it there. And so your image is
going to be what's inside there.
>> Okay.
>> And the image should pop up here. Let's
see what happens. You know, I never take
the X-rays. So I'm like, wait,
[laughter] I hope I know how to use this
thing.
>> I don't know why that's not go.
Yeah. See, it's blocking X-ray.
>> What?
>> The sensor did not detect the radiation.
>> Yeah, that's what happened. So, there's
your finger. So,
>> whoa. Can we try and see if it's
>> I know did not make an X-ray proof
artifact.
>> That would be the most savage joke ever.
>> Okay, he got through that one.
>> Yeah. All you're seeing is I mean I'm
seeing porocity, you know, which makes
sense because you're seeing different
levels of density in the material. If
you go back to the X-ray of your finger,
porocity, it's just different levels of
density. Take one of that.
>> Yeah. Yes, I do.
>> See what happens.
>> What if they had picked a material that
they knew would not be penetrated by
X-ray at that thickness?
>> All right.
>> You're seeing that.
>> Okay.
>> The way it was sitting,
>> I got you. So, we're looking at it from
this section right here pretty much.
That would be our right here. I don't
see anything in there. Do you? Parker
said he saw a light. He thought he saw a
light bulb
>> LED in there.
>> We'd see it, wouldn't we?
>> Metal would pop up. I can promise you
that about like that. And maybe it won't
have as much of that stone to go
through.
>> Yes.
>> There's nothing. And there's not a split
in it either.
>> If there's any metal in there, that
should
do.
>> So, that's looking straight through it.
And there's still no bright white metal
straight through there.
>> That's what it looks like.
>> It's solid. There's nothing in there. Do
you know anything about the specs on
this? Just for my own kind of knowledge.
>> 125 volts, 60 Hz, 7.5 amps.
>> I understand X-rays now. After Parkers,
now I get it. Look, that's 70 kilts.
That's a lot of volts. They're moving
really quick, but tiny ampacity. 7
milliamps. That's what makes it safe.
71,000 is 700,000
volts. Thatz that's the energy
transforming immediately cuz it's coming
in at 125 volts and going to 700,000
volts. 70,000 volts. Yeah.
>> Image that way. Let me turn it that way.
>> Dude, let's see.
I know what that is.
>> Okay. That looks like metal.
>> So that is what metal would look like.
>> After test number four, we still have
absolutely no conclusion. Do you want to
[laughter] do you want to try and shoot
through that big crystal?
>> Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> I didn't didn't go through that
>> side angle. Try it.
>> That's going to matter. But we can try.
>> I want to see cuz it
>> it's not detected.
>> Nope.
>> Let's try it on the skinny side.
>> Okay.
>> Something there.
>> Nothing.
>> Kind of looks like the other crystal.
You're just
>> I want to know if it's split. If it was
split, we'd see that, wouldn't we?
>> You would probably see a density
difference. You probably see the line.
>> Let's see if there's a way we can tell
if there's a battery in there. If I can
eliminate that from the list of
possibilities, it would make the search
a little
>> less complicated.
>> Nope.
>> Try to get just the corner of it.
>> Mhm.
>> Yep. Come on, baby.
>> Picking up a little of that metal, but
we're getting we're mainly getting the
stone right here.
>> This is the first rednecking I've ever
done in a dental office.
radiator, baby. Come on.
>> Okay, now you're seeing something.
>> Oh, there. Now, what is that? We need a
batteryologist.
>> So, that's the surface. So, that's what
you're seeing at the surface. That's the
interesting part right there. So, you're
seeing metallic looking, which would be
going down into the stone. But then,
>> what is that?
>> A battery will pick up his metal. You'll
see a battery. It's full of lead.
>> That could be a less dense metal than
what that is. That could be a metal.
Although most metals do show up brighter
than that. This has got some structure.
That's what is that? You know, I don't
know.
>> The inside of a battery contains metal.
The outside contains insulation.
>> You'd think it'd look like the other
way. Do you have a battery that we could
like just a Duracell battery?
>> Metal ring insulation. Hell, let's see.
That's what I thought.
But can you pull up the other one or put
the other one side by side next to it?
If it was a battery, it'd be it'd be
real light on the inside because it has
metal. That other one was light on the
inside and this one is dark cuz a
battery has to be insulated. The battery
is is is a light color because it's
metallic. That is a dark color
>> and a battery would run out. Correct.
>> I mean,
>> yeah. How would you charge it? You see
how everything else on here is one color
and then just this side it looks like
it's, you know, iron deposits. It also
kind of looks like rusty metal to me.
Come on, baby.
>> H. No.
>> Well, hold on. What color is metal and
what color is stone? This side over here
doesn't look like it has any of that
metalish stuff in there. Can we pop that
side and just see?
thing.
>> Same thing.
>> You're seeing the double density.
>> The thinner versus the thicker.
>> Oh, hold on. Right.
>> What is that?
>> That's You're seeing the metal. You see
it's just an odd shape. Almost like it's
welded in there.
>> Oh. Do you think they're an obvious
fake?
>> I do not. I don't know what they'd be
trying to fake. I can't look at them and
tell you they were made 5,000 years ago
or 100 years ago, but I don't think they
were just made.
>> Would you agree this is a well-made
piece of art at the very least?
>> Absolutely.
>> Extremely unique.
>> Absolutely. Yeah.
>> If this was for sale at a store
somewhere just randomly as a, you know,
a knickknack in Los Angeles, what do you
think it would sell for? It'
>> be very expensive. I would think it'd be
unique.
>> The time required to make it.
>> Quite a while. Especially considering it
lights up and we don't know how.
[laughter]
Who's told you it's fake? Like, who's
been trying to tell you it's fake?
>> Well, that that's uh I don't know.
People who still live with their mom in
their basement? Um, you know,
>> I mean, who have you been showing it to?
I guess
>> the entire world. Nobody who sees them
in person thinks they're fake. Do you
want anything more?
>> No, I think that's it.
>> Dude, thank you so much for your time
and coming in on Sunday. Hey, look.
Geared up.
>> We're going to go for a run. Hey, old
times.